"星舰迷航"有新的内幕消息说
New more details about the new star trek film.
会有描写史巴克出生的镜头
There's going to be a scene depicting spock's birth.
我还是对描写
I'd be more interested
史巴克是如何被怀上的镜头更感兴趣
In a scene depicting spock's conception.
“星舰迷航”主人公之一 是Vulcan族
算了吧
Oh, please.
对于瓦肯人  交配  或者你可以说"pon fahr"...
For vulcans, mating-- or if you will, pon fahr--
瓦肯人是 "星舰"系列中的瓦肯星人形生物  Pon farr 瓦肯人七年一次的发情期
这是超隐私的事情
It's an extremely private matter.
但我还是想知道细节
Still, I'd like to know the details.
他母亲是个人类
His mother was human.
他父亲是个瓦肯人
His father is vulcan.
他们不能随便就怀上了
They couldn't just conceive.
也许他们得去个诊所
Maybe they had to go to a clinic.
想象下史巴克的父亲身处一个小屋
Can you imagine spock's dad in a little room
里面全是长着尖耳和肥臀的怪物
With a copy of pointy ears and shapely rears.
怎么在星舰迷航里
How come on star trek
每个人的私密部位都长得一样啊?
Everybody's private parts are the same?
没有哪一个外星妞对柯克舰长(男主角)说过
No alien lady ever told captain kirk,
"把你那玩意从我鼻孔里拔出来"
"hey, get your thing out of my nose."
你们好  能不能帮帮忙?
Hi. can you help me?
我正在写电子邮件  然后a键坏了
I was writing an e-mail and the "a" key got stuck.
现在一按就"aaa..."
Now it's just going "aaa..."
什么东西洒上面了?
What'd you spill on it?
没啊
Nothing.
健怡可乐
Diet coke.
还有酸奶
And yogurt.
还有点指甲油
And a little nail polish.
我先看看吧
I'll take a look at it.
先生们  请注意本地书呆子新闻
Gentlemen, switching to local nerd news--
今年的大学物理碗比赛  渔夫  陈  肖杜里和麦克奈
Fishman, chen, chaudury and mcnair aren't fielding a team
不打算组队参加了
In the university physics bowl this year.
不会吧  为什么啊
You're kidding. why not?
他们成立了一个理发店轻唱组
They formed a barbershop quartet and got a gig
并将在诺氏果园表演
Playing knott's berry farm.
南加州一主题公园
这么说在你们的圈子里
Wow, so in your world
你们已经算是潮人了
You're like the cool guys.
正解
Recognize.
今年我们赢定了
This is our year.
那些家伙不参加  整个物理碗
With those guys out, the entire physics bowl
就将跪倒臣服于扎德了
Will kneel before zod.
扎德?
Zod?
超人里的一个大反派  说来话长
Kryptonian villain. long story.
挺有趣的
Good story.
我可不去
Well, count me out.
什么  为什么
What? why?
你们想利用我的聪明才智
You want me to use my intelligence
去参加那么庸俗的比赛?
In a tawdry competition?
你会叫毕加索
Would you ask
去玩看图猜字吗
Picasso to play pictionary?
你会叫韦伯斯特(词典编纂者)去玩猜字游戏吗
Would you ask noah webster to play boggle?
Noah Webster 美国词典编纂之父  Jacques Cousteau 法国海军将领 海洋生物学家
你会叫雅克·库斯托(知名潜水家)去玩钓鱼?
Would you ask jacques cousteau to play go fish?
别这样  你需要一个四人团队
Come on, you need a four-person team.
我们正好四个人
We're four people.
照你这么说  我们还得玩桥牌
By that reasoning we should also
举着一个天蓬
Play bridge, hold up a chuppah
去参加奥林匹克雪车速滑赛
And enter the olympic bobsled competition.
别忘了给我弄张票
Tickets to that, please.
谢尔顿  你什么意思  需要我引用
Sheldon, what, do I need to quote
史巴克临死前的一席话吗
Spock's dying words to you?
美国儿科专家 教育家和作家
别  不要
No, don't.
"...重于少数人的利益
"the needs of the many...
"...少数人的需求要重要
"...outweigh the needs of the few.
...或个人的利益"
...or the one."
该死  我去吧
Damn it, I'll do it.
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第13集
The.Bat.Jar.Conjecture
参加物理碗比赛的头等大事儿
Okay, first order of physics bowl business
就是我们得起个拉风的队名
We need a truly kick-ass team name.
有什么想法没?
Suggestions?
叫永动机队怎么样?
How about the perpetual motion squad?
它超越了物理学的理论
It's beyond the laws of physics, plus
而且对女士们也是一种暗示
A little heads-up for the ladies.
女士们?
The ladies?
"永动机队...我们可以干一整夜"
"perpetual motion squad-- we can go all night."
我喜欢
I like it.
我不喜欢
I don't.
按照传统  一般都是以凶猛的动物取名
Teams are traditionally named after fierce creatures,
以此来威慑对手
Thus intimidating one's opponent.
那我们应该叫孟加拉虎队
Then we could be the bengal tigers.
太垃圾了
Poor choice.
从合力来说
Gram for gram,
没有动物可以强过
No animal exceeds the relative fighting strength
热带行军蚁群
Of the army ant.
也许是吧
Maybe so,
但是你用放大镜
But you can't incinerate a bengal tiger
没法把孟加拉虎点着
With a magnifying glass.
我们还是投票吧
Let's put it to a vote.
-喜欢...  -你先等等
All those in favor... point of order.
我觉得团队的名字
I move that any vote on team names
需要意见完全统一
Must be unanimous.
你们不能在按常理
No man should be forced to emblazon his chest
都会选择热带行军蚁群的情况下
With a bengal tiger when common sense dictates
强制别人在胸口印一只孟加拉虎
It should be an army ant.
这位从不接受别人意见的绅士
Will the gentleman from the great state of denial
愿意屈服一次吗
Yield for a question?
我会屈服
I will yield.
当我们经过这
After we go through the exercise
无聊烦人的投票之后
Of an annoying series of votes,
这位绅士肯定会输
All of which the gentleman will lose,
然后当不能按照他的方式来
Does he then intend to threaten to quit
-他是否就要用退出来威胁大家?  -他会的
If he does not get his way? he does.
我同意热带行军蚁群  你们呢?
I move we are the army ants. all those in favor?
下午好  欢迎你们
Good afternoon, and welcome
来到今天的物理碗大赛练习赛
To today's physics bowl practice round.
我叫佩妮  将担任主持人
I'm penny, and I'll be your host
因为很明显  我周六下午
Because apparently I didn't have anything else to do
也没什么其它的事儿干
On a saturday afternoon,
这是不是有点悲哀?
And isn't that just a little sad?
先生们  准备好了吗
Gentlemen, are you ready?
-当然  -快开始吧
Yes. of course. fire away.
这可能不关我的事
You know, it's none of my business,
但有个男人在女人面前都不说话
But isn't a guy who can't speak
会不会让你们感觉有些自信心不足?
In front of women going to hold you back a little?
只要女人待在人群里
Oh, he'll be okay
他就应该没事儿
Once the women are mixed into the crowd.
只有当跟女人一对一并且那人闻起来很香时
He only has a problem when they're one-on-one
他才会出问题
And smell nice.
谢了  拉杰  是香草味的油
Ah, thanks, raj. it's vanilla oil.
其实我才是那个注意到的人
I was actually the one who noticed.
好的  开始吧
Okay, let's just start.
好  第一题
Okay, the first question
是关于光学的问题
Is on the topic of optics.
有史以来最短的光脉冲是多少?
"what is the shortest light pulse ever produced?"
库珀博士
Dr. cooper.
毫无疑问  答案是130百亿亿分之一秒
And of course the answer is 130 attoseconds.
-回答正确  -我也知道的
That is correct. I knew that, too.
你真棒  亲爱的
Good for you, sweetie.
好了  下个问题
Ok, next question.
何种量子力学效应
"what is the quantum mechanical effect
被应用在硬盘存储加密上?
"used to encode data on hard-disk drives?"
霍华德
Howard?
毫无疑问  答案是
And of course the answer is
-巨磁阻  -正确
Giant magnetoresistance. right.
我先抢到的
Hey, I buzzed in.
然后我回答了  这叫团队合作
And I answered. it's called teamwork.
你难道不觉得应该
Don't you think I should answer
由我来回答工程问题吗  我是个工程师
The engineering questions? I am an engineer.
照这个逻辑  那我应该回答
By that logic I should answer
所有人类学的问题  因为我是哺乳动物
All the anthropology questions because I'm a mammal.
问下一题吧
Just ask another one.
好的
Okay.
哪颗人造卫星记录下了
"what artificial satellite has seen glimpses
爱因斯坦预言的时空结构拖曳现象?
Of einstein's predicted frame dragging?"
致密天体 例如黑洞与中子星 它们的自转能吸引附近的空间与时间 围绕它们一同转
2004年发射升空 任务是探测地球附近的时空曲率
答案是引力探测器B卫星
And of course, it's gravity probe b.
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
你得让其他人也参与答题
You have to let somebody else answer.
为什么
Why?
因为这是礼貌
Because it's polite.
这跟礼貌有什么关系
What do manners have to do with it?
这是战争
This is war.
当罗马人在迦太基(北非一古城)地上撒盐
Were the romans polite when they salted the ground
确保以后寸草不生的时候他们讲礼貌了吗
Of carthage to make sure nothing would ever grow again?
莱纳德  你说过我只负责提问的
Leonard, you said I only had to ask questions.
竞赛的目的就是为了给出正确答案
The objective of the competition is to give correct answers.
如果我知道  我为什么不说出来
If I know them, why shouldn't I give them?
因为也许我们也知道正确答案
Some of us might have the correct answers, too.
别逗了  你连博士学位都没有
Oh, please. you don't even have a phd.
好吧  够了!
All right, that's it!
-霍华德  坐下  -好吧
Howard, sit down. okay.
也许我们需要稍微休息一下
Maybe we should take a little break.
好主意  我得活动下腕关节
Good idea. I need my wrist brace.
按这些键弄得我以前
All this button-pushing
玩任天堂留下的老伤更严重了
Is aggravating my old nintendo injury.
我同意
I agree.
他说什么
What did he say?
他把谢尔顿比喻成
He compared sheldon
某种可能会在夏夜用到的
To a disposable feminine cleansing product
"夏依"女性清洁用品
One might use on a summer's eve.
没错  还有那进来的套套
Yeah, and the bag it came in.
莱纳德  太好了
Leonard, excellent.
我想给你看样东西
I want to show you something.
等等行吗  我想跟你谈谈
Can it wait? I need to talk to you.
快看
Just look.
我刚为我们队设计了一款完美的队服
I've designed the perfect uniforms for our team.
颜色是基于"星际旅行"原始系列
The colors are based on star trek the original series.
你们三个穿上陪衬的红色
The three of you will wear support red,
我穿象征命令的金色
And I will wear command gold.
"AA"是什么意思?
Why do they say "aa"?
行军蚁
Army ants.
会不会容易产生歧义?
Isn't that confusing?
AA对某些人
"aa" might mean
可能表示其它的什么意思
Something else to certain people.
为什么一支物理碗比赛队
Why would a physics bowl team
会起名为阳极氧化铝呢
Be called anodized aluminum?
不  我是指...
No, I meant...
算了
Never mind.
来看看这个
Hey, check it out,
我给你买了个蝙蝠侠饼干罐
I got you a batman cookie jar.
太屌了
Oh, neat!
什么节日啊
What's the occasion?
朋友嘛  你又喜欢蝙蝠侠
Well, you're a friend, and you like batman
还有饼干  你被剔除出队了
And cookies, and you're off the team.
什么?
What?
霍华德  拉杰和我刚开了个团队会议
Howard, raj and I just had a team meeting.
-不  你们没开  -是  我们确实开了  我刚从那回来
No, you didn't. yes, we did. I just came from there.
好吧  不管你从哪里回来
Okay, I don't know where you just came from,
但是你们不可能开团队会议的
But it could not have have been a team meeting
因为我也是队员  并且我不在场
Because I'm on the team and I wasn't there.
因此  这个队并没有会
Ergo, the team did not meet.
好吧  我这么说吧
OK. let me try it this way.
我跟几个朋友一起喝了杯咖啡聊了聊
I was at a coffee klatch with a couple of friends,
然后由一件事谈到了另一件
And one thing led to another,
最后你就被剔除出队了
And it turns out you're off the team.
为什么啊?
Why?
因为你弄得大家都没有兴致了
Because you're taking all the fun out of it.
抱歉
I'm sorry,
难道物理碗的获胜者
Is the winner of the physics bowl
是最有兴致的那支队伍?
The team that has the most fun?
好吧  我这么说吧
OK. let me try it this way.
你太招人烦了
You're annoying
没人愿意再跟你合作了
And no one wants to play with you anymore.
我知道了
I see.
这么说那我得通知你下
Well, at this point I should inform you
我打算组建自己的队伍
That I intend to form my own team
然后把组成你们的
And destroy the molecular bonds
一切分子键弄得粉碎
That bind your very matter together
把形成的胡乱状态的粒子全都变成你们的眼泪
And reduce the resulting particulate chaos to tears.
多谢提醒
Thanks for the heads-up.
不用谢
You're welcome.
-还有一件事  -什么?
One more thing. yes?
放马过来吧  婊子
It's on . B.I.T.C.H.
谁会跟他一组参赛呢
So who'd he get to be on his team?
他不说
He won't say.
他只是笑着从他的蝙蝠侠罐里拿蛋白杏仁饼干吃
He just smiles and eats macaroons out of his bat jar.
他在跟你打心理战
He's using psychological warfare.
我们必须以牙还牙
We must reply in kind.
我是说等他看咱们的时候
I say we wait until he looks at us,
咱们也笑  好像在说"是  你是个聪明强大的对手"
Then laugh like, "yes, you are a smart and strong competitor,
"但我们也一样"
"but we are also smart and strong,
"我们非常有可能击败你"
And we have a reasonable chance of defeating you."
那我们到底该怎么笑呢
How exactly would that laugh go?
这听起来更像是  "我们是一个
That sounds more like, "we are a tall,
"101忠狗"中的邪恶女老板
想拨了你的达尔马提亚狗皮做大衣的瘦高个女人"
Thin woman who wants to make a coat out of your dalmatians."
哥几个别忘了
Guys, let's remember
谢尔顿毕竟还是我们的朋友和我的室友
That sheldon is still our friend and my roommate.
那怎么了?
So?
没事
So nothing.
让我们整垮他吧
Let's destroy him.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我们得赶紧找一个最佳第四人
Okay, we're going to need a strong fourth for our team.
你们知道谁一看就很聪明吗
You know who is apparently very smart
我觉得演Blossom的那个女孩很聪明
Is the girl who played tv's blossom.
她有博士学位  神经学科或者其它什么
She got a phd. in neuroscience or something.
拉杰  我们不能让情景喜剧演员
Raj, we're not getting tv's blossom
加入我们的物理碗比赛队的
To join our physics bowl team.
那个主演"纯真年代"的女孩怎么样
How about the girl from the wonder years?
先生们  我相信我找到可以解决
Gentlemen, I believe I've found the solution
所有问题的办法了
To all our problems.
我们不能去找莱斯利·温克
We can't ask leslie winkle.
为什么?  就因为你和她睡过
Why? because you slept together,
而当她和你做完后
And when she was done with you
把你像隔夜的酸辣酱那样扔了?
She discarded you like last night's chutney?
是
Yes.
有时为了团队必须得牺牲个人
Sometimes you've got to take one for the team.
是啊  有点男人样  伙计
Yeah, sack up, dude.
好吧
Fine.
我去  为了团队牺牲自己...
Here I go, taking one for the team...
男人
In the sack.
好  莱斯利
Hey, leslie.
你们好
Hi, guys.
莱斯利  我有个问题问你
So, leslie, I have a question for you,
可能会
And it might be
有些尴尬  考虑到我...
A little awkward, you know, given that i...
干过你
Hit that thang.
莱纳德  没有任何理由只因为我们
Leonard, there's no reason to feel uncomfortable
看过彼此在极度激动的快感下
Just because we've seen each other's faces
那扭曲的脸和裸体就感到有什么尴尬的
And naked bodies contorted in the sweet agony of coitus.
没有吗
There's not?
天  听上去肯定应该很尴尬才是
Gee, 'cause it sure sounds like there should be.
放心  我们性生活的任何内容
Rest assured that any aspects of our sexual relationship
包括你的喜好
Regarding your preferences,
你的手法  你的表现
Your idiosyncrasies, your performance
仍然在卧室所固有的
Are still protected by the inherent
隐蔽下被保护着
Confidentiality of the bedroom.
这话说得真好  但如果可以的话
That's all very comforting, but if it's okay,
我想开始说我的问题了
I'd like to get on to my question now.
说吧
Proceed.
我们正准备参加物理碗比赛
We are entering the physics bowl,
而我们队现在三缺一
And we need a fourth for our team.
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
我在研究象征轻子超对称性
I'm really busy with my like-sign dilepton
真的很忙
Supersymmetry search.
轻子  人人都能"搞"的研究  我们需要你
Dilepton, shmylepton. we need you.
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧  我们尽力了
Well, we tried.
只能去和谢尔顿面对面单练
We'll just have to face sheldon mano y mano
单练单挑了
Y mano a mano.
等等  你们是要对抗谢尔顿·库珀?
Wait, you're going up against sheldon cooper?
没错
Yes.
那个狂傲  轻视女性 东德克萨斯州来的蠢驴
That arrogant, misogynistic, east texas doorknob
让我放弃我的高能粒子研究
That told me I should abandon my work
去洗衣服带孩子的白痴?
With high-energy particles for laundry and childbearing?
她加入了
She's in.
感觉如何?
so, how do you feel?
严阵以待?
Nice and loose?
一鼓作气?
Come to play?
士气如虹?
Got your game face on?
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
是的  你其实不必都待在这儿啊
Yeah. you know, you don't have to stay for the whole thing.
不  不  我想待
Oh, no, no. I want to.
感觉很有意思
Sounds really interesting.
先生们
Gentlemen.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
我去坐了
I'm just gonna sit down.
这就是你的队伍了?
So, is that your team?
事实上  我根本不需要队伍
Actually, I don't need a team.
我能单手把你们轻松解决了
I could easily defeat you single-handedly,
但规则说要四个人
But the rules require four.
所以  请允许我介绍三楼门卫
So, may I introduce the third-floor janitor,
午餐食堂大妈  还有"我西班牙语不太好"的
The lady from the lunch room, and my spanish is not good--
儿子或者男人
Either her son or her butcher.
你们的队伍呢
And what about your team?
你们那艘破船又纳入了哪位鼠辈?
What rat have you recruited to the s.s. sinking ship?
你好  谢尔顿
Hello, sheldon.
莱斯利·温克
Leslie winkle.
没错  莱斯利·温克
Yeah, leslie winkle.
就是那位
The answer to the question,
让谢尔顿·库珀哭得像个小娘们儿似的人
"who made sheldon cooper cry like a little girl?"
没错  我是聚合树脂
Yes, well, I'm polymerized tree sap,
而你是无机胶粘剂
And you're an inorganic adhesive.
因此无论你用嘴巴发射什么子弹过来
So whatever verbal projectile you launch in my direction
都会被我弹开
Is reflected off of me,
而回归其原先的轨道
Returns on its original trajectory
对准着你
And adheres to you.
噢  疼!
Oh, ouch!
好了  有请各就各位
Okay, if everyone could please take your seats.
这是你的队服
Here's your t-shirt.
PMS(有经前综合症的意思)?
Pms?
还要过几天呢...
It's a couple days early...
不是  这意思是"永动机队"
No. it stands for "perpetual motion squad."
对  当然了
Oh, right, of course.
我在想什么呢
What was I thinking?
下午好  各位
Good afternoon, everyone,
欢迎光临今年的物理碗
And welcome to this year's physics bowl!
今天的第一场比赛可谓双雄争霸
Today's preliminary match features two great teams.
AA队对...
Aa versus...
PMS队
Pms.
通宵达旦  同志们
All night long, y'all!
好的  我们直接开始
Okay, well, let's jump right in.
第一个问题
First question
分值为10分
for ten points.
π零介子的同重旋单重配合物是什么?
"what is the iso-spin singlet partner of the pi-zero meson?"
PMS队
Pms?
埃塔介子
The eta meson.
回答正确
Correct.
提出正式抗议
Formal protest.
什么理由
On what grounds?
我袖口的维可牢(尼龙搭扣)
The velcro on my wrist brace
粘住我的衣服了
Caught on my shirt.
抗议无效
Denied.
好  这题还是10分
All right, for ten points,
地球上存在的最轻且没有
"what is the lightest element on earth
稳定同位素的元素是什么
With no stable isotope?"
AA队
Aa?
毫无疑问  答案是锝
And of course, the answer is technetium.
完全正确
Terrific.
下一题
Next question.
由于量子真空波动造成两块无电荷板间
"what is the force between two uncharged plates
所产生的力是什么
Due to quantum vacuum fluctuations?"
PMS队
Pms?
谢尔顿真烂...卡西米尔效应
Sheldon can suck on... the casimir effect.
正确
Correct.
量子电脑如何分解大数?
How does a quantum computer factor large numbers?
PMS队
Pms?
肖氏算法
Shor's algorithm.
正确
Correct!
4.1855乘以10的7次方尔格(功的单位)每卡路里
4.1855 times ten to the seventh ergs per calorie.
普雷沃斯特交换理论
Prevost's theory of exchanges.
当物体与其周围物体处于平衡 它以相等速率辐射和吸收辐射能 因而它的温度保持不变
λ等于πrn平方分之一
Lambda equals one over pi r squared n.
760摄氏度...
760 degrees celsius...
差不多是这位坐在前排的年轻女士的体温
The approximate temperature of the young lady in the front row.
沃尔维茨先生  这是第二次警告你了
Mr. wolowitz, this is your second warning.
西格玛粒子
A sigma particle.
是的  假设一个虚拟的星球
Yes, assuming the hypothetical planet
其质量大于地球
Has a mass greater than the earth.
正确
Correct.
女士们先生们  我手里拿着最后一道问题
Ladies and gentlemen, I hold in my hand the final question.
现在比分显示  AA队  1150分  PMS队  1175分
The score now stands. Aa 1,150, pms 1,175.
因此  赢得这100分即赢得比赛
So, for 100 points and the match,
请仔细思考屏幕上显示的方程式
Please turn your attention to the formula on the screens.
解出这个方程
Solve the equation.
见鬼
Holy crap.
这该死的什么玩意
What the hell is that?
看上去像是在罗斯威尔太空船上发现的东西
Looks like something they found on the ship at roswell.
"天煞地球反击战(独立日)"中的外星太空船
加油  想想
Come on. think.
莱斯利?
Leslie?
莱纳德  你急我是没用的
Leonard, it's not gonna work if you rush me.
你只能等我慢慢来
You have to let me get there.
你是不是不提那个不行?
You are never gonna let that go, are you?
还剩10秒
Ten seconds.
PMS队
Pms?
抱歉  太紧张了
Sorry, I panicked.
猜一个
Then guess.
八
Eight.
点四
.4
抱歉  答案错误
I'm sorry, that's incorrect.
AA队  如果你们能回答正确  你们就赢得比赛
Aa.If you can answer correctly, the match is yours.
他不知道
He doesn't have it.
他哑口无言了
He's got squat.
AA队  我需要你们的答案
Aa, I need your answer.
答案是-8πα
The answer is minus eight pi alpha.
等等  等一等
Hang on. hang on a second.
这不是我们的答案
That's not our answer.
你这是干什么
What are you doing?
回答问题
Answering question.
赢得物理碗
Winning physics bowl.
你怎么会懂什么物理?
How do you know anything about physics?
我在这里是门卫
Here I am janitor.
在前苏联  我是物理学家
In former soviet union, I am physicist.
列宁格勒工业大学
Leningrad politechnika.
加油  北极熊
Go polar bears.
这故事真是美妙
Well, that's a delightful little story,
不过我们之前说好  你坐在这
But our arrangement was that you sit here
一个字别说  我来回答问题
And not say anything-- I answer the questions.
你刚没回答问题
You didn't answer question.
听着  也许在你亲爱的俄罗斯
Hey, look, now, maybe you have democracy now
现在已经搞民主了
In your beloved russia,
不过在这支物理碗队伍里  由我铁腕统治
But on this physics bowl team, I rule with an iron fist.
AA队  我需要你们的最终答案
Aa, I need your official answer.
反正不是他说的
Well, it's not what he said.
-那是什么呢  -我想要另一个问题
Then what is it? I want a different question.
你不能回答另外一个问题
You can't have a different question.
提出正式抗议
Formal protest.
抗议无效
Denied.
提出非正式抗议
Informal protest.
抗议无效
Denied.
我需要你们的最终答案
I need your official answer.
不  我拒绝回答
No. I decline to provide one.
那太遗憾了  因为你的队友
Well, that's too bad because the answer
给出的是正确答案
Your teammate gave was correct.
那是你的看法
That's your opinion.
好了  比赛的获胜方是...
All right, the winner of the match is...
等等
Hang on.
谢尔顿  证明你一个人的聪明
Sheldon, is proving that you are single-handedly smarter
能轻松高过每一个人
Than everyone else so important
重要到你情愿由于你一个人
That you would rather lose by yourself
而使整个队伍输掉比赛?
Than win as part of a team?
我没明白你的问题
I don't understand the question.
继续吧
Go ahead.
获胜方是PMS队
The winner is pms.
对不起  有人坐那儿
Sorry, somebody's sitting there.
谁
Who?
我的物理碗奖杯
My physics bowl trophy.
这奖杯毫无意义
That trophy is meaningless.
是我放水了  所以你没赢
I forfeited, therefore you did not win.
-我知道有人不同意  -谁?
I know someone who would disagree. who?
我的物理碗奖杯
My physics bowl trophy.
莱纳德真聪明
Leonard is so smart.
谢尔顿是谁
Sheldon who?
好了  这太幼稚了
All right, that is very immature.
没错  对不起
You're right. I'm sorry.
我没有!
I'm not!
好  来场新的比赛
Okay, new contest.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
我来让你们一决雌雄
I am settling once and for all
看谁是这里最聪明的  如何?
Who is the smartest around here, okay?
-准备好了没  -当然
Are you ready? Absolutely.
-放马过来  -好
Bring it on. okay.
玛莎  简  和辛迪是哪部电视剧中的
"marsha, jan and cindy were the three daughters
三姐妹?
In what tv family?"
是"脱线家族"
The brady bunch.
好
Okay.
萨米·黑格取代大卫·李·罗斯
"sammy hagar replaced david lee roth
成为了哪个乐队的主唱?
As the lead singer in what group?"
"脱线家族"?
The brady bunch?
是范海伦
Van halen.
好
All right.
麦当娜嫁给了哪位"开放的美国学府"子弟?
"madonna was married to this ridgemont high alum."
我的天!  肖恩·潘!
Oh, my god! sean penn!
你怎么会知道这些东西的?
How do you know these things?
因为我出去  跟别人有交流
I go outside, and I talk to people.
好吧  这个
Okay, here.
哪位演员被
"what actor holds the record
"人物"杂志评为当前最性感男人?
For being named people magazine's sexiest man alive?"
-威廉·夏纳 -等等
William shatner. wait.
William Shatner "星舰迷航"1966-1969中Kirk舰长的扮演者
Patrick Stewart "星舰迷航之下一代" 中Picard舰长的扮演者
我觉得不是威廉·夏纳
I don't think it's shatner.
那应该就是帕特里克·斯图尔特
Then it's got to be patrick stewart.
不是
No.
提出正式抗议
Formal protest.
好
All right.
哪位歌手演唱的"Oops, I did it again"?
"singer who sang, oops, I did it again'"?
好
Okay.
"翠笛鸟认为它看到了什么?"
"tweetie bird tought he taw a what?"
"空中大灌篮"中大舌头的鸟 其实答案是 迈克尔·乔丹
罗慕伦人
Romulan.
正确
Yes.
是的 它"认为"它"看"到了罗慕伦人...
He tought he taw a romulan.